Time's up.
Those cowards aren't coming to save you.
All units, ready!
Fire!
Run! Run!
This way!
Run! Hurry!
Come on!
Run that way!
Spread out, quick!
Watch out!
Yu Mo
What do you want to be when you grow up?
I want to be a police officer.
Comrade Li Mingyuan is hereby appointed
as Deputy Chief of Rongcheng Police,
effective immediately.
I thought
a new deputy chief would change things,
but crows are black the world over.
My mom won't let me work at the station.
She says no one there is any good.
I'm no commander.
I'm just an ordinary police officer.
I'm the Deputy Chief of Rongcheng Police.
Protecting the people is my duty.
I can't leave.
Thanks to the timely intel you provided,
we wiped out the Japanese in one swoop
and spared Rongcheng from the war.
Word came from our informant.
The civilians were safely rescued.
The Rongcheng police force...
all gave their lives for our country.
Brothers!
Reinforcements will be here soon!
Our mission is to help our reinforcements
by pinning down the Japanese in the city
and opening Rongcheng's gates for them!
I ask you all
to cooperate with Captain Xu
and fight alongside the CPC Guerrillas!
Slay the invaders!
Defend our homeland!
Move out!
Let's move out too.
Hurry, go find Lian Yu!
Lian Yu! Lian Yu!
Who are you?
Lian Yu, do you remember me?
Don't be afraid. Go ahead and eat.
Lian Yu.
I'm a friend of your brother, Lian Ye.
I'm here to save you.
Come over here, quick.
Yuna.
Pick up the knife.
Kill him.
What are you waiting for?
Kill him!
Lian Yu!
Kill him, Yuna!
Kill him!
Little Lian Yu...
"The sun illuminates the day,
the moon brightens the night."
Mother combed through the scriptures
to give you this name
so your heart would seek the light.
Remember this:
You are Chinese,
not Japanese!
Yuna!
Kill him!
Lian Yu!
I'm your brother, Lian Ye!
My name is Lian Yu!
Are you all right?
We're fine.
Let's go.
Rendezvous with Captain Xu at the tower.
Move, move!
Go!
Captain Xu,
you're here.
The snipers on the gate tower
have killed so many of our men.
It's almost dawn,
and we still can't push through!
Leave it to me. I'll take them out.
All right.
Protect him!
Hurry, over here!
Captain, the snipers are dead!
Brothers, charge!
Charge! Charge! Charge!
Brother!
Brother Lian!
All right.
I promise you.
I will protect the Sanshan Gang.
Comrades, reinforcements are here!
Reinforcements are here!
Charge! Charge!
Brother!
Brother Lian!
Brother! Brother Lian!
Brother Lian! Brother!
Brother Lian!
Brother!
Brother! Brother Lian!
September 3, 1941.
Rongcheng was liberated.
The surviving members of the Sanshan Gang
joined the CPC Guerrillas.
Their underworld lives came to an end,
yet the nation lives on,
and their bond endures forever.
They're all here.